

Randyl P. Boadilla

CONTACT ME

- **(** 09275388373/09760674980
- boadilla.randyl@gmail.com
- Empire Hilltop, Payatas B, Quezon City

EDUCATION

St. Dominic Institute - Fairview (2015-2019)

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, *Dean's Lister*

Justice Cecilia Munoz Palma High School (2010-2014)

SKILLS

- Proficient in troubleshooting and resolving technical issues.
- Strong knowledge of computer hardware, software, and operating systems.
- Excellent customer service and interpersonal skills.
- Ability to communicate technical information to non-technical users effectively.
- Experience with remote desktop support tools and techniques.
- Experience in diagnosing and resolving hardware and softwarerelated problems.

PROFILE

A dedicated and highly skilled Computer Technician with 4 years of experience in diagnosing, repairing, and maintaining a wide range of computer hardware and software systems. Experienced at providing technical support to end-users, troubleshooting complex issues, and ensuring optimal system performance.

PORTFOLIO

https://shiroedyl.github.io/Me/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Associate/Computer Technician October 2019 - Present

GJAX Computer Trading

- Answering customer inquiries and resolving product issues.
- Arranging product displays to attract customer attention.
- Keeping track of product inventory and restocking shelves as needed.
- Identifying opportunities to upsell additional products or services.
- Demonstrating expertise in photo editing for product posting and advertisement in Social Media.
- Consistently working to meet or exceed assigned sales targets and quotas.
- Performing basic computer hardware repairs, such as replacing components (e.g., RAM, Storage, GPU, etc..).
- Arranging for more complex repairs through authorized service providers.
- Assisting customers with software-related problems, including operating system issues and software installations.
- Providing guidance on updating or upgrading software.

OJT Trainee, Technical Support **DENR, Central Office**

July 2018 - October 2018

- Basic troubleshooting of Computer Hardware
- Assisting end-users with network-related issues, including connectivity problems, VPN setup, and Wi-Fi access.
- Providing guidance on connecting devices to the network.
- Diagnosing and resolving network connectivity issues, including hardware and software problems.
- Investigating and fixing network outages or disruptions.

CERTIFICATIONS EARNED

 Certificate of Completion on Programming Foundations with JavaScript, HTML and CSS (Coursera Course) - 2024 https://coursera.org/verify/ZA4UC741VKOF

Professional references available upon request.